The config file "setting.cfg" must be put under folder \bin. Currently supported fields are as follows:

wowdir
	directory of wow. Application use this folder to search mpqs. If this is absent or wrong dir, application use local directory.

locale
	Application's locale, e.g zhCN, enCN, enUS. After setting this, application will read mpqs under aproprepiate locale folder.
	This field may be absent or null value. Default value: zhCN	
